{
    "question": "Contoh percakapan \"Expressions of surprise\" Untuk dua orang?",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "Dina : Hi dani did you know that everyone in this school is talking about you because\u00a0you are the winner of the sains olympiad?<br>Dani : Wow, what a surprise i can&#039;t believe it<br>Dina : Yeah you are the winner good job my friend<br>Dani : Thanks a lot dina<br>Dina : You&#039;re welcome dani",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "bagaima-membalas-surat-kepada-pembeli-tersebut-kiara-agusta-jal-156",
            "question": "Bagaima membalas surat kepada pembeli tersebut??    kiara agusta\r\njalan W.Z Johanes No. 621\r\nThe Tiny Tots Toy Company\r\nJalan Kuningan Sari No. 50, Jakarta\r\nDear Costumer Service Respresentative,\r\n\r\nI recently purchased one of your Tiny Tents (Model #47485) for my three-year old daughter. Unfortunately, after viewing the components that came with the product, I discovered that four of the parts were missing. Also, the instructions that came with the tent are in portuguese and Russian, but not in english or french, the two languages I speak. These two unforeseen problems have resulted in the tent remeaning unassembled and unacceptable as a toy my daughter.\r\nI am writing to request replacements for the missing parts, and a copy of the full set of assembly instructions (in english or french) for the model I purchased. If reasonable arrangements are not made within ten bussines days, I will return the tent to the store I purchased it from and expect a full refund. To assist you in processing my request, I am including a copy of my sales receipt and a list of the missing parts.\r\nI have purchased other toys manufactured by your company in the past, and have always been impressed with the quality and selection that Tiny Tots has made available to its customers. I sincerely hope this is a one-time incident, and that any future purchases I make will live up to the standard my family has come to expect from your company.\r\n\r\nSincerely,\r\nKiara Agusta",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Dear Kiara Agusta,<br><br>I am glad that you let us know about this matter. We are more than happy to assist you and would like to keep you impress with our service. We apologize for the missing part of the screw which supposed to be attached to the tents. We will send it tomorrow. And also the copy of the instruction will be delivered together with these missing parts. Hopefully you are satisfied with our reply and always be our loyal customer<br><br>Regards<br><br>Toytots Representative<br>Laura <br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bisa-gak-buatin-pidato-dari-teks-ini-plastic-surgery-is-not-s-r-624",
            "question": "Bisa gak buatin pidato dari teks ini\u00a0    plastic surgery is not s recent phenimenon, but it was appeared since 3000 years ago. in the past, it was for medical purpose but now it is creating beuty and trend to modify some part of body.\r\nmany people nowaday want to be extraordinary such as animal or less human by plastic surgery. they modifying their faces and bodies to make them more animal like. meny so called 'lizard people' have had their tongues split. a woman who changed her face like a cat. other people gone beyond different kinds of tattoos.\r\nthe people who done outcast actually they lack self respect and have adesperate need for attention. they should be treated by psychiatrist, not plastic surgeons. and we should be aware of society that no longer wants to look human",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "hi people, today i will tell you about plastic surgery. plastic surgery appeared 3000 years ago, in the past, it was for medical purpose but now it is only for a change of appearance. many people nowdays want to have a beautiful or handsome face, in other words &#039;being closer to perfections in the matter of appearance&#039;. but some people have some really weird tastes and they tried to be less human-like, by using plastic surgery, they tried to looks like a lizard or cats, and many other animals. the people that took plastic surgery is usually people who is not satisfied with their looks, or their body. they degraded\u00a0the gods creation, and try to be more &#039;perfect&#039;, however they sometime did not look at the risk. you see, if the surgery failed, then can you even imagine what your body or face would look like? and because of that i highly recommend not to take plastic surgery, and appreciate what god has given to us.\u00a0\u00a0<br><br>^aku tambahin beberapa informasi\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "mohon-berikan-contoh-soal-mengenai-persuading-459",
            "question": "Mohon berikan contoh soal mengenai persuading",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Persuading adalah mempengaruhi lawan bicara untuk melakukan atau mengerjakan sesuatu seperti yang diharapkan pihak pertama<br><br>COntoh\u00a0<br>Mengajak bermain basket<br>Hi my brother, would you be so kind to accompany me playing basketball? I will give you a chocolate if you would like to play it with me.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "when do you go to school about 10 minutes later?",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-bahasa-inggrisnya-mengacak-acak-rambutnya-667",
            "question": "Apa Bahasa Inggrisnya mengacak-acak rambutnya?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "bahasa inggris nya adalah mess her/his hair",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Ruffled/Mess his/her hair<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "aku-dapt-tugas-dari-guru-binggris-ku-disusruh-membuat-cerita-sp-750",
            "question": "aku dapt tugas dari guru b.inggris ku disusruh membuat cerita \"spoof\" dari pngalaman pribadi, tapi aku bingung gimana crtanya. tlg bantu ya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "kamu pasti punya kan pengalaman lucu ,,, kamu tulis aja bhs indonesianya nntik saya coba nerjemahin<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-percakapan-making-and-handling-cancellation-gimana-ya-ada-918",
            "question": "Contoh percakapan making and handling cancellation gimana ya?\r\nada yang bisa bantu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "David : Excuse me. I think there is a mistake in our bill. We didn&#039;t have dinner here lst night.<br>Receptionist : I&#039;m sorry, sir. Here&#039;s the bill from the hotel restaurant. It&#039;s got your signature on it.<br>David : But that&#039;s not my signature. I&#039;d like to speak to the manager.<br>Receptionist : I&#039;m sorry, sir. The manager is busy.<br>Manager : You have a complaint about your bill, sir ?<br>David : Yes. I&#039;m afraid there&#039;s a mistake. We didn&#039;t have dinner in the restaurant last night.<br>Manager : But this looks like your signature on the restaurant bill.<br>Let me see. Oh dear I&#039;m very sorry. There&#039;s another couple called Morris in the hotel.<br>They had dinner last night. Not you. I do apologize.<br><br>sudah ya cukup :)\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "arrange-the-jumbled-words-to-form-meaningful-sentencesstarting-w-193",
            "question": "arrange the jumbled words to form meaningful sentences,starting with the underlined words. 1. phone-puppet-his-invite-the-I-number-my-see-Finto-know-will-if-show-to-I-at-place 2. and-holiday-Bali-if-have-will-his-Lombok-long-go-year-Mr. Kukuh-family-to-they-and-this-a \u00a0 mohon di bantu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "2. Mr. Kukuh and his family will go to Bali and Lombok if they have a long holiday this year<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-dialog-expression-suggestion-170",
            "question": "Contoh dialog expression suggestion?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "I have been usiung asparagus extract ( 2capsules per day in the morning ) on the suggestion of my doctor who is aDO.<br>This has helped reduce the amount of fluid retention. Seacoast vitamins has consistently had the lowest price for the same brand I was buying at the heralthfood store.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-bantuannya-jelaskan-pengertian-spoof-text-dan-contohnya-899",
            "question": "Tolong bantuannya, jelaskan pengertian spoof text dan contohnya, trmksh",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Spoof Text, Penjelasan + Contoh Lengkap- Pernahkah kalian melihat salah satu program komedi, Seketsa? Pastinya kalian tidak asing kan. Jalan cerita di Seketsa itu lah yang dinamakanSpoof Text. Awal cerita dimulai dengan adegan atau kejadian yang biasa kemudian menjelang akhir ada adegan atau kejadian yang tidak dikira yang membuat cerita tersebut lucu.<br><br>Untuk melengkapi penjelasan mengenai\u00a0Jenis Teks Bahasa Inggris (Types of Text), pada kesempatan kali ini penulis hadirkan penjelasan dan contoh\u00a0Spoof Text\u00a0lengkap.<br><br>A. Pengertian Spoof Text<br><br>Selain\u00a0Narrative Text,\u00a0Recount Text, dan\u00a0Anecdote Text,\u00a0Spoof Text\u00a0juga termasuk ke dalam golongan\u00a0Narration\u00a0(lihat\u00a0Jenis Teks Bahasa Inggris,\u00a0Types of Text), yang tentunya menceritakan kejadian di masa lampau dengan akhir yang lucu dan tidak disangka-sangka.<br><br>B. Tujuan Komunikatif Spoof Text<br><br>Tentunya semua jenis teks yang tergolong\u00a0Narration\u00a0memiliki tujuan komunikatif yang sama, begitu juga pada\u00a0Spoof Text, yaitu untuk menghibur pembaca atau pendengar dari cerita yang dibacakan.<br><br>C. Struktur Kebahasaan Spoof Text<br><br>Terdapat tiga jenis struktur kebahasaan yang dimiliki oleh\u00a0Spoof Text, yaitu:<br><br>1. Orientation<br><br>Seperti halnya jenis teks\u00a0Narration\u00a0yang lain, selalu diawali dengan\u00a0orientation.\u00a0Orientationadalah bagian di mana penulis memulai memperkenalkan cerita.<br><br>2. Events<br><br>Sedangkan pada bagian\u00a0Events\u00a0yaitu bagian di mana penulis menceritakan kejadian-kejadian dalam cerita tersebut tetapi kejadian yang diceritakan masih kejadian yang wajar.<br><br>3. Twist\u00a0<br><br>Dan bagian dari\u00a0Spoof Text\u00a0yang terakhir adalah\u00a0Twist.\u00a0Twist\u00a0merupakan bagian teks yang mana menceritakan kebalikan dari kejadian-kejadian wajar di bagian\u00a0Events.\u00a0Twistmerupakan bagian akhir dari\u00a0Spoof Text\u00a0yang menceritakan kejadian akhir lucu dan tidak disangka-sangka sebelumnya.\u00a0<br><br>D. Ciri Kebahasaan Spoof Text<br><br>Terdapat beberapa ciri kebahasaan\u00a0Spoof Text\u00a0yang bisa membedakan dengan\u00a0Jenis Teks Bahasa Inggris (Types of Text)\u00a0yang lainnya, yaitu:<br><br>1. Menggunakan\u00a0Past Tense; was, were, did, etc.<br><br>2. Menggunakan kata kerja aksi (action verb);\u00a0did, went, walked, etc.<br><br>3. Menggunakan kata keterangan waktu dan kata keterangan tempat.<br><br>4. Diceritakan secara kronologis.</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "spoof text adalah jenis teks yang menceritakan kejadian masa lalu yang lucu dan terjadinya tidak terprediksi.<br>contohnya cerita tentang hal konyol yang kamu alami seperti terpeleset di depan umum, dsb<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bantuin-aku-dong-cari-biografi-aknes-monica-menggunakan-bahasa-in-292",
            "question": "Bantuin aku dong cari Biografi aknes monica menggunakan Bahasa inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Agnes Monica Muljoto. Born in Jakarta 1 July 1986, known abroad as Agnes Mo. She stared her career in the entertainment industry at the age of six as a child singer. She jobs is singer, actress, dancer, voice actress, and producer.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}